stardoll.com 2017-06-28

# Membership Agreement - Stardoll | English

## MEMBERSHIP AGREEMENT

#### MEMBERSHIP AGREEMENT

##### MEMBERSHIP CONDITIONS

##### 1\. Read this first!

These conditions represent an Agreement between you and Stardoll. Stardoll produces and operates www.stardoll.com as well as various mobile apps. The website is called the “Service” in this Agreement. This agreement refers to the website. Please find our mobile application privacy policy [here](http://www.stardoll.com/en/help/termsOfUseMobile.php?). The website is intended for the enjoyment of children aged 13-18. Many of the mobile applications are directed to teenagers, and some are directed to a general audience of all ages. Because younger children are attracted to the Service, Stardoll takes steps described below to secure the safety of and protect the privacy of potential younger members. 

Regardless of the user’s age, Stardoll requires that all users agree to these Membership Terms and, where a user cannot in its own right enter into this Agreement, that their parent also read and accept these conditions since they constitute a legally binding Agreement. For this reason, it is very important that you go through the conditions in this Agreement together with your parents so that you know what you can and cannot do on the Stardoll Service. Ask your parents to go through the conditions with you carefully and to help you register. When you register, activate your account and accept this Agreement, you become a member. This means that you accept the conditions below and that you confirm that your parents have also read and accepted the conditions, if you are under the age of being eligible to enter into this Agreement in your jurisdiction. By becoming a member you, or a parent or guardian on your behalf, are promising and agreeing also to follow and accept the other rules which Stardoll publishes on its Service. This Agreement also applies when you purchase products on Stardoll's Service; see below under “Terms of Sale.” If you don't accept this Agreement, you should not register as a member on Stardoll. 

Stardoll reserves the right to make changes to these membership terms if Stardoll deems it necessary or if it is required by law. In the case of material change, Stardoll will notify you of the change in advance of the change becoming effective. If you do not want to accept the change, you may terminate your membership with immediate effect at any time before the change becomes effective. By using the services available on Stardoll’s Service, such as Stardollars and virtual products (virtual clothes and all other goods and services on Stardoll's Service), you accept the membership terms and agree to comply with them.

Stardoll solely decides on the content of the Stardoll Service, such as for example new games, products, including the rules of such games and products. Stardoll further reserves its right to develop, delete, amend and otherwise make changes to the Service without any prior notice to you or other members. Your membership, me-doll, virtual products and Star-dollars are part of a service provided to you on Stardoll’s Service and you only receive a right to use them according to these conditions and the terms on the Service from time to time.

##### 2\. Special information for PARENTS

Stardoll uses both technical filters and moderators who supervise what happens on Stardoll's Service in order to offer a nice and safe environment. The moderators also answer members' reports of unpleasant and unsuitable behavior but we still urge all parents to be actively involved in following their children's activity on the Internet.

Stardoll is dedicated to protecting the privacy of all of its members and handling any personal information we obtain from our members with care and respect. The information and the terms in this Agreement that we conclude with our members fulfills the high standard of protection provided for in the European Union and in the United States. 

For citizens in the US, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act rules apply to children under the age of 13. From the terms on Personal Data and Privacy Policy below, you can see what information we collect from our members, what we do with it and the limited involvement of third parties. If your child is of an age that requires parental consent in order to have full access to the website, the account might be automatically be flagged as a pending and limited membership account subject to parental consent to activate a full membership account. The “Notice to Parents” e-mail that you receive from us contains a more detailed description of the types of activities offered. Until such parental consent is obtained, your child will only have access to certain features of the Service.

If you would like to see what information Stardoll has about your child, you can contact Stardoll at the same e-mail address indicated above: [parentalrights@stardoll.com](mailto:parentalrights@stardoll.com) or send us a letter to:

STARDOLL AB  
Luntmakargatan 26  
S 111 37 Stockholm  
SWEDEN  
or fax at one of the following numbers:  
Fax number: USA (+1 - 212 - 208 4566)  
Fax number: Great Britain (+44 - 20 - 7990 9907)  
Fax number: Argentina (+54 - 11 - 40321600) 

If your child has become a member of Stardoll and if you do not accept this Agreement please contact us at: parentalrights@stardoll.com. 

For the security of our members Stardoll retains the right to require the identification of parents. We are not entitled to disclose other children's/members' personal data to you as a parent. Stardoll can only disclose personal data belonging to children other than your own if a legal and/or police obligation exists to do so.

##### Privo's Privacy Assurance Program

Stardoll AB (http://www.stardoll.com) is a Member of the PRIVO’s PRIVO-Cert™ Safe Harbor Certification Program (“the Program”). As a participating member in the Program, Stardoll AB adheres to the strict information collection, use and disclosure requirements set forth by the Program. PRIVO is an independent, third-party organization committed to safeguarding children's personal information collected online. PRIVO aims to help parents and their children exercise control over personal information while exploring the Internet. The PRIVO certification seal posted on this page indicates that Stardoll AB has established COPPA compliant privacy practices and has agreed to submit to PRIVO’s oversight and consumer dispute resolution process. If you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us at privacy@stardoll.com. If you have further concerns after you have contacted Stardoll, you can contact PRIVO directly at privacy@privo.com.

##### 3\. Personal data and Privacy Policy (including Kid’s Privacy Policy)

In order to register and participate as a member of Stardoll, we might ask you to provide us with the following personal data:

\- Your first name  
\- your e-mail  
\- parent e-mail address  
\- your mobile phone number  
\- your user/display name  
\- your age  
\- your gender  
\- the country where you live  

By providing Stardoll with personal data as defined above, to the extent permitted by law, you give Stardoll permission to use the above personal data so that Stardoll can send out news, contests, offers and advertising to your e-mail address and/or mobile phone via sms, mms or similar messaging system, and you allow Stardoll to adjust the content and advertising on its Service to your or others' age group and gender. Examples of such communication are, for instance or promotional newsletter e-mails to notify you that new or improved services are available on or coming to Stardoll, that Stardoll is carrying out membership surveys in order to improve our services, or that Stardoll is creating targeted content and offers for you based on information about how you act on the Service, what your age is and where you are located geographically. You may opt-out from the Stardoll e-mail program at any time, either by following unsubscribe links within received e-mails, or by adjusting your Stardoll email settings.

The same applies in those cases where Stardoll co-operates with another company to provide you with interesting offers. Such companies do not have access to your personal data other than for assisting Stardoll with its mailings, banner marketing and the like which you have given Stardoll permission to by this agreement. Such companies will not have the right to retain and use the data for any other purposes than the assignment for Stardoll.

Stardoll agrees not to sell or transfer your personal data, including e-mail addresses, to a third party who is not a strict service provider to Stardoll and bound by this policy. It can happen that Stardoll comes to rely on other companies in order to carry out various tasks such as, for example, help with marketing, the performing of technical services for our Service, etc. These companies can in certain cases gain access to personal data which they need in order to complete an assignment for Stardoll. Stardoll treats all personal data with the greatest care and signs agreements with other companies which mean that they can only use your data in order to complete the assignment for Stardoll.

The same applies in those cases where Stardoll co-operates with another company to provide you with interesting offers. Such companies do not have access to your personal data other than for assisting Stardoll with its mailings, banner marketing and the like which you have given Stardoll permission to by this Agreement. Such companies will not have the right to retain and use the data for any other purposes than the assignment for Stardoll.

If all or essentially all resources of the Stardoll company, that is to say, the entire Service, are acquired by another company (a so-called acquisition of assets and liabilities), the personal data required in order to continue to operate Stardoll are acquired by the buyer and that buyer will continue to be bound by this privacy policy.

Stardoll stores personal data gathered from members for such period as is prescribed by applicable law. During this period personal data are only used to the extent permitted by these terms and by applicable law as well as for the security of members, that is, in order to prevent, investigate, uncover and prosecute potential crimes against one of our members. Stardoll reserves the right to disclose your personal data as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our site.

Members of Stardoll whose accounts contain information indicating to Stardoll that they are old enough, may log in using an existing account on a community service, for example by using Facebook Connect, whether on Facebook or on another community site that uses Facebook Connect (each such site referred to as a "Connect Service" below). Once you allow Stardoll to connect with a Connect Service, you will be able to use your Connect Service login information to log into Stardoll as a member, and you will be able to publish your activity on Stardoll to your Connect Service profile. Additionally, by using a Connect Service, you permit Stardoll to access information related to you (including your profile information, friends, and privacy settings) from the Connect Service so you can use your information on Stardoll, and so that we can help improve your use of Stardoll and allow you to interact with your Connect Service friends on Stardoll. All such Connect Service personal data will be handled in accordance with Stardoll’s general privacy policy as described in this Agreement and you agree that Stardoll can use the data as described above in this section of the Agreement. In order to make the Connect Service possible, you agree to allow the Connect Service Provider, such as Facebook, to check your Facebook cookies when you are visiting the Stardoll Service, and allow Facebook to receive information concerning the actions you take on the Service . The information shared with the Connect Service provider will be transmitted to and stored by the Connect Service Provider on servers that may be placed outside your country of residence. 

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected by Stardoll through your Connect Service login, however, your activities on the Connect Service provider’s site, such as Facebook, are covered by their privacy policy and other terms of use.

Stardoll reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here at this URL, by means of a notice on our home page or as required by law. If any changes are unacceptable to you, you shall stop using this Service. Your continuing use of the Stardoll Service, can, to the extent permitted by law, be deemed as an acceptance of these terms, including changes.

##### 4\. Questions concerning personal data and revoking approval

If you, or your parent/guardian if you are not eligible to enter into this Agreement, want to know what information Stardoll has about you or have other questions about your personal data, you can contact us [here](mailto:parentalrights@stardoll.com).You can withdraw your permission for Stardoll to collect, use and share your personal information (so-call personal data). In that case click [here](http://ox.stardoll.com/www/delivery/ck.php?bannerid=39245) and fill in the form. This is because, in order to be able to offer the best possible member experience on Stardoll, we need to be able to store personal data about you and to be able to communicate with you as a member. Therefore, if you do not allow us to process personal data about you, we have to cancel your membership if you do not wish to allow us to process your personal data. See more under clause 10 below.

##### 5\. Cookies (applies also to users as non-members)

By using the Stardoll Service and/or accepting this Membership Agreement you give Stardoll the right to place a text file in the web browser on your computer or device, i e cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies (below “Cookies”). Like most other online Services, Stardoll uses two different types of these Cookies to improve and customize your experience of the Service. With persistent cookies we keep track of, for example, how many visitors we have to the Service and of which parts of the Service is most popular. This type of information can be sent out by Stardoll in a revised (that is to say, aggregated and non-personal) version as statistics to members, collaborative partners, sponsors and others. 

This means that we or our third party service providers and/or our partners, may use cookies to manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through the Service. This also helps us, our service providers and partners to provide more relevant advertising. For more information regarding third-party ad servers, see below "Collection of Information by Third-Parties".

You can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or block all cookies. Blocking all cookies will affect your online experience and may prevent you from enjoying the full features offered at our Service. 

##### 5.1. Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Ad Servers and Sponsors

We, our third party service providers and/or partners may place cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies (below “Cookies”) to help present advertisements on the Service, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. Stardoll and its vendors/contractors follow this Privacy Policy as stated in these Membership terms, which for the avoidance of doubt apply also to non-members of the Stardoll Service. 

The Stardoll Service can contain links to other Services, including those of sponsors and advertisers, who are not acting as vendors to Stardoll under Stardoll’s Privacy Policy, and whose information practices may be different from ours. These third party services may conduct contests or sweepstakes that are promoted on the Stardoll Service. Stardoll or our advertisers may use third parties to serve or present the ads that appear on our site and to conduct research about the advertisements. These third parties may view, edit or set their own cookies. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy policy. Visitors should consult those other third party services' privacy notices, since those services are not covered by our Privacy Policy and may follow different procedures. These are the third parties we work with: Webads, PilMedia, Netcom Media, Massmovement, ToTwenty, Gamebiz, AdWeb, Egmont, Ad2one Ireland, Publicidad, Venatus, Genz Media, Evolve, Brighttroll, Google ADX, Smartclip, Ooyala, Neutrino. We only work with these third parties in selected territories. For more information on any of our third parties please contact us [here](mailto:parentalrights@stardoll.com)

##### 5.2. Limitations to the use of Information and Cookies (applies also to non-members)

Stardoll’s collection and use of Cookies as defined in this clause is subject to applicable local law, this means for example that Stardoll shall limit the use of any third party services mentioned above to users under a certain age if/when required by law.

##### 6\. Rules of conduct

As a member you should follow Stardoll's [ONE-STOP rules](http://ox.stardoll.com/www/delivery/ck.php?bannerid=39249) (rules of conduct) as published from time to time on Stardoll's Service.

Stardoll is entitled to inspect writings, pictures and other member-generated material and to remove material which in our sole opinion breach the ONE-STOP-rules.

Stardoll has the right to contact and hand out information posted on the Service to Police or similar authorities if we suspect that a crime has been committed, and please note that it does not require a legal offense to have your account terminated.

Writings and postings relating to serious problems related, but not limited to eating disorders, self harm, suicide etc are directed by Stardoll to sites and forums with grown up professionals especially trained to deal with this. Stardoll will publish appropriate links to local sites handling these kinds of serious problems.

All community features on Stardoll, including but not limited to, Friends, Blog, Guestbook, Album, Parties, Suite Chats display a purple triangle with an exclamation sign button for reporting purposes. All members are asked to read our [guidelines](http://ox.stardoll.com/www/delivery/ck.php?bannerid=39250) regarding reports and reporting before reporting inappropriate behavior.

You can block/unblock another member from sending messages to you, for more information about how, please read more [here](http://ox.stardoll.com/www/delivery/ck.php?bannerid=39250).

Your Stardoll account is neither inheritable nor transferable. If you allow another person to use your account you are responsible for all acts of this person in relation to Stardoll and to the terms of use.

You must not reveal or trade passwords or reference numbers, change email to scam email addresses, enter password on phishing sites or use proxies or in any other way treat your account, password and other personal belongings in a careless manner. This may lead to loss of account and/or items and Stardollars. Stardoll can not be held responsible for the contents of your account and will not refund lost items or Stardollars if your password, reference number, email etc has been used by a third party. Stardoll will do its best to restore lost accounts, provided that you claim of such lost account is sent to Stardoll within 3 months after the loss. 

##### 7\. Rules and responsibilities for member-generated material

You are responsible for whatever material you create yourself and publish (upload) on to Stardoll's Services, for example, dolls, clothes, blogger texts, chat sessions and the like, sceneries and pictures. Whoever violates Stardoll's rules of conduct can be expelled as a member; for more about this see below under item 10.

##### 8\. Rights to member-generated material

You own the rights to the material which you have created yourself on Stardoll's services, but in this agreement you give Stardoll the right, without special compensation, to publish the material for an unlimited time throughout the world and irrespective of the medium used, that is, whether on the Internet, on TV or through mobile distribution, etc. This means that you give Stardoll the right to use, copy, present, reproduce, display, edit, integrate, license as well as distribute that material which you have created. These rights of Stardoll apply to both commercial and noncommercial use.

##### 9\. Rights to Stardoll's material

You may not use Stardoll's dolls, clothes, information, data, names, pictures, logotypes or icons from Stardoll's Services (we call these “Stardoll's Material”) if it is not clear from the Services that this is permitted. This means that you can not copy, distribute, disseminate, sell, publish, send or otherwise circulate Stardoll's Material to another person without the written consent of Stardoll. Nor may you change, revise or replace any of the Material found on the Service, either in its entirety or parts thereof.

##### 10\. Suspension and cancellation of membership

Stardoll has the right to cancel your membership and close your account if you violate this agreement or the regulations on Stardoll's Services or if you have not used your account for four months or more. We can also close your account if you fail to pay for the goods and services that you buy or if you shop without the permission of the person who is paying according to item 16 below.

When your membership is cancelled, whatever time remains on your Superstar membership is forfeited and the Stardollars in your account disappear.

Stardoll has the right to save the personal data of a suspended member even after the account has been closed; see item 3 above.

##### 11\. Choice-of-law and jurisdiction

Subject to local mandatory law, this Agreement is regulated and interpreted according to the laws in Sweden and the courts in Stockholm will have exclusive jurisdiction, unless you live in UK, US or Germany in which case the local laws will apply and the jurisdiction shall be as follows; in US the state and federal courts located in the state of California, in Germany the regional courts of Dusseldorf and in UK the courts of England and Wales. If any part of this Agreement should be considered invalid, this will not affect the validity of the remaining sections of the Agreement.

##### 12\. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY and DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY

Stardoll decides solely on the content of the Stardoll Services and reserves its right to develop, delete, amend and otherwise make changes to the Service without any prior notice to you or other members. Potential errors on Stardoll's Services are taken care of as soon as possible, but Stardoll does not guarantee that Stardoll's Services always work.

Material published on Stardoll's Services can refer to products, programs or services no longer available in certain countries. 

You use the Stardoll Services at your own risk. Stardoll does not warrant the accuracy or timeliness of the Service.

All submissions by you or other members are solely the expressions of the sender and Stardoll can not be held responsible or liable for the content in such submissions. All content on the Stardoll Services, including without limitation third party content, submissions and any information or material contained on the Services, are provided to you on an “as is” basis with no warranties of any kind. Stardoll, neither by itself or its licensors, agencies or other representatives, makes no express, implied or statutory representations, warranties or guarantees in connection with the Stardoll Services, including without limitation the Stardoll content and third party content. Stardoll does not provide any warranties against viruses, spyware or malware that may be installed on your computer.

##### 13\. Links to third party websites

Stardoll's Service may contain links or references to other Services. When you use these links, you are leaving our Service. Stardoll has no control over information published on other third party Services and assumes no responsibility for information and other content on such other third party Services. You assume the risk yourself when using other websites linked to this Service. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of other services you visit. Stardoll will limit the use of such third party services as required by law when parental consent is needed.

#### TERMS OF SALE

##### 14\. Prices and delivery

Stardoll has the right to determine the prices and other terms of sale of the Service itself and to change them. If certain products need to be shipped, then the shipping costs are not included in the price of the product, but all such costs are added to your bill and can be viewed when you complete your purchase.

We accept a variety of different methods of payment. Examples of some of these are credit cards, mobile phones, telephones, gift cards, pre-paid cards and PayPal. Locally available forms of payment are displayed at any given point on the payment page for your country. For EU residents VAT is included in accordance with currently applicable tax legislation. This will be displayed along with the price. When you pay by mobile phone and telephony, VAT or sales tax are included according to local regulations.

The virtual products you buy become available to you as soon as possible. Star dollars and virtual products (virtual clothes and all other goods and services on Stardoll's Service) may not be exchanged unless Stardoll decides to allow for exchanges in particular cases. Stardoll is entitled to make such decisions itself on a case-by-case basis.

All virtual products and Stardollars are part of the service provided to you on Stardoll’s Service and you only receive a right to use them according to the terms of the Service from time to time. The virtual products and the Stardollars do not have any monetary value and may not be exchanged for money. The availability of virtual products and the type and range of items available for purchase may be changed by Stardoll without notice. Any virtual products purchased within a Superstar membership may be modified or become unavailable for use once your superstar membership expires.

Stardollars have an expiration date of 12 months after purchase and gift cards are valid for 6 months after purchase.

##### 15\. Credit card security

We want you to feel secure and safe when you shop on Stardoll. You can give us your credit card information when you shop with us. We use state-of-the-art security systems available on the market and your data are protected on our servers throughout the order process with the help of encryption and firewall technology. On most web browsers a small lock is displayed on the menu bar (task bar) at the very bottom of the screen when you visit a secure site. Look to see if this icon is present when you visit a website where you are invited to give out personal information. We also use the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption in order to protect your personal data from use by unauthorized persons.

##### 16\. Approval by the person liable for payment

You must have gained permission from the recipient of the invoice, the cardholder or the primary account holder of the phone used before you purchase a Superstar membership or Stardollars. If you make purchases without such approval, Stardoll is entitled to cancel your membership account.

##### 17\. Returns

We accept returns for products you have purchased that are not virtual products purchased on the Service and provided that these products along with the packaging is returned in its original condition within 14 days of the shipping date. We send you a return form together with the products you buy which you must enclose together with the products that you are returning.

##### 18\. Cancellation of monthly payments

To cancel a monthly payment please click [here](http://ox.stardoll.com/www/delivery/ck.php?bannerid=39251) and click the “Cancel monthly refill” link in the “You are a Superstar” box.

##### 19\. Delivery and errors

When Stardoll cannot deliver products that have been ordered in the desired amounts, we reserve the right to supply equivalent substitute products or to remove that portion of the order which cannot be delivered. We cannot be held accountable for orders which are delayed or which cannot be delivered because of circumstances beyond Stardoll's control (for example but not limited, natural disasters, wars, civil disturbances, the exercise of public authority, terrorism, fires, storms, floods, explosions, strikes, work stoppages and other labor conflicts, breakdowns in equipment, services or transport or other such causes).

##### 20\. General

This Service is operated by Stardoll AB from its office in Stockholm, Sweden.  
Stardoll AB   
Luntmakargatan 26   
S 111 37 Stockholm   
Sweden   
E-mail: [info@stardoll.com](mailto:info@stardoll.com)  
Fax number: USA (+1 - 212 - 208 4566)  
Fax number: Great Britain (+44 - 20 - 7990 9907)  
Fax number: Argentina (+54 - 11 - 40321600)  

DO NOT USE THIS SERVICE IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE ABOVE CONDITIONS!
